KIAN'S B&B
No way.
More guests?
Hello?
HI?
Hello.
What? English?
IS IT A FOREIGN GUEST?
SORRY
Well…
She's speaking English.
NATURALLY PASSES THE PHONE
I haven't been abroad in so long
that I forgot how to speak English.
LEAVES
Tell her we'll send her the address.
- Your English is good.
- Not at all.
I think we should send her
the address right now.
- I'll send it.
- Is it this one?
Gosh, I haven't been abroad in a while,
so I forgot how to speak English.
I was struggling to speak English,
so I was a bit flustered.
To the young viewers
who are watching this,
study hard while you're still young.
It's hard to learn when you're older.
Because of the number of rooms we have,
I don't think we can fit many guests.
Can we fit them all?
- If so, they'll all have to sleep outside.
- Yeah.
We only have seven beds.
Maybe we should…
Let's give them our rooms.
We'll just take our stuff out.
THEY DECIDE TO MOVE OUT
- Then…
- Let's let the girls sleep there.
Yeah, let them sleep there.
We'll move out. Should we sleep here?
Okay.
THEIR NEW SPACE
We can bear it for the others.
Gosh. Thanks, Jun-ho.
For what?
For toughing it out.
Well, we didn't know
there would be more guests.
Exactly.
THE BOSS PUTS OUT HIS FAVORITE PICTURE
MOVES HIS BUDDHA STATUE
AND ORGANIZES HIS CLOTHES
We can use these socks as blankets.
4:00 P.M.
THIRD PAIR OF GUESTS APPROACH KIAN'S B&B
Don't you feel
this is something like Squid Game?
WELCOME TO KIAN'S B&B
KNOCK, KNOCK
They're here.
"Can you open Kian's B&B?"
PRACTICING WHAT TO SAY IN ENGLISH
"Welcome to Kian's B&B."
OPENS
PEEKING OUT
OPEN DOOR
Okay?
Geez, my English is this bad?
TRYING TO OPEN THE DOOR
- I think they're bumping into the door.
- Right?
- We can't become soft.
- Right.
- We can't get soft.
- You're right.
In Season 1, Jin always emphasized that.
- You shouldn't compromise.
- I shouldn't?
- Then, you wouldn't be the owner.
- True.
- Right, we saw that.
- We can't get soft.
If it were Jin, I'm sure
he would've locked the door.
You shouldn't compromise.
ARE YOU WATCHING, JIN?
IT'S OPENING!
Hello.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
THIRD PAIR OF GUESTS
This was so smart! How did you make this?
How did you make this?
Your Korean is good.
Her Korean is so good.
THE GUESTS' KOREAN IS GOOD
I should close the door for her.
Let me help you.
- Watch your hands. Be careful.
- How did you close this?
One, two.
LIFTING HIM UP
- Pull.
- Let's go.
Hey, are you okay?
SURPRISED
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
- Are you okay? Goodness.
- Gosh.
I'm all right.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Let's try it again.
- Again?
Let's try again.
One, two, three!
Three!
Hold on. Wait.
My goodness.
- Goodness. What is going on?
- Slowly.
Wait. Pull.
Slowly.
Wait. Slowly.
- Your foot.
- We got it.
Your foot.
- Wait, I…
- Close it.
Wait, let me down.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm all right.
SMITA, SNEHAL
What?
What's that?
- They're comforters.
- Comforters.
- Our comforters?
- Yes.
I love it!
They're huge. Isn't this fun?
It looked like a studio apartment,
but it was so big.
The comforters
and toilet paper were huge too.
It was beyond my imagination,
and I really liked it.
Hey, our new guests are here.
Hello!
Hello.
- Hello.
- I know you!
I think I've seen you before!
Isn't that Jun-ho?
IS THAT JUN-HO?
YES, IT'S JUN-HO!
- What?
- It's Jun-ho!
This is crazy!
I was so surprised. I never imagined it.
Nice to meet you.
FINALLY GREETING THE BOSS
- Hello.
- Yeah.
- I'm a fan.
Nice to meet you.
- Okay.
- Most recently.
Nepal?
- You're close.
Yes.
Why is your Korean so good?
First off…
- Shoe size?
It's 245 mm.
- It's 245?
- Yes.
- It's 245.
- Okay.
Thank you.
For the sauna.
There's a sauna?
There are actually three beds left.
One's in the fridge.
And the second and third are in there.
Those without rooms…
Actually, this whole house is one room.
- Right.
- So you can sleep out here too.
- The two of us…
- We could go in there.
THEY CHOOSE THE TV CABINET
- Thank you.
We really enjoyed Season 1.
- Really?
- Yes.
We saw how getting into the house
was the toughest part.
- Yes.
- So we were thinking
this time would be…
- Tough?
- There would be some kind of mission.
Kian4…
- Eight?
- They called you Boss.
KIAN48 MEANS 79 YEARS OLD
If it was 48, I'd be an old man.
It's 84.
- It's 84!
- 84! Sorry, numbers are still confusing.
Gosh, 48.
I watched the old show you were on
so many times.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you!
I'm shy.
I'm off to cook.
HERE TO COOK DINNER
- Do you know how to cook rice?
- I don't.
We should wash these first.
WASHING NEW DISHES BEFORE COOKING
Put water in there.
- In here?
- That's right.
This doesn't swivel?
Well…
- It doesn't swivel.
- It doesn't.
- There's no tap here.
- No.
ODDLY POSITIONED TAP
- Geez.
- The position's so…
Boss.
CALLING THE BOSS
- We have a problem here.
- What?
THE BOSS IS ON THE WAY
HE FINDS THE TAP FIXED IN PLACE
Right, it's for both.
When we do the dishes,
we might use too much water
if we do it under a running tap.
So for the water,
we'll collect water in this bowl
shaped like a soy sauce dipping dish
and use it for as long as we can.
HE ONLY BUILT A TAP FOR THE JACUZZI
TO CONSERVE WATER
DIFFICULTY: HARD
Boss didn't think this through.
Should I cook the rice?
I'm good at it.
Yes, please.
HE MAKES RICE OUT OF GUILT
Done.
Is the water amount right?
- The water? Yeah.
- Okay.
THE BOSS'S RICE IS READY TO BE COOKED
JUN-HO JOINS THE KITCHEN
- What should I do?
- You can rinse these.
- Rinse them?
- Yeah.
I should…
- I should rinse them here.
- Right.
- I'll just put them all in.
- Yeah.
YEON-KOUNG WASHES
AND PUTS THEM IN THE BOWL
THEN JUN-HO RINSES THEM
I'll put them over here.
ORGANIZES THEM ON THE SIDE
SQUATTING
RINSING
STANDING UP
ORGANIZING
Geez.
SQUATTING WHILE DISHWASHING
I'm so hot.
SUNKEN EYES
Are you okay, Jun-ho?
I'm so hot, Yeon-koung.
GETTING A COLD BREEZE
KIAN'S B&B
THE BOSS RELIEVES THE TIRED JUN-HO
- We're washing them. Yeah.
- Since they're new?
This will make them ready to use.
HE STARTS RINSING THEM
Put something else on. It keeps turning.
It shouldn't turn.
HE JUST RINSES THEM IN SOAP WATER
SHE DIDN'T SEE IT
It shouldn't turn.
- That's not how you rinse them.
- Then how?
Rinse them once more.
Right, okay.
Kian, I'll do them.
These are done. Can you put them there?
KICKED OUT
These too.
He only rinsed them with this water.
It's okay. They're young.
These weren't washed?
Hey, the water's flowing over here.
Jun-ho, turn off the water.
What on earth?
Wait, what happened?
Turn off the water.
- Geez.
- It's flooding.
It's spilling out.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WATER LEVEL RISES
AND OVERFLOWS
The spoons and…
We can just rinse them.
- Just rinse?
- Yes.
These?
The water leaked down this way, right?
- We should do it here.
- It's from this.
We should use this. Let's…
- It doesn't swivel.
- Darn it.
It doesn't swivel.
I tried.
Hey, it's a flood!
We've been flooded.
Goodness, it's a flood.
FLOOD CLEANUP
WRINGING OUT
WRINGING OUT AGAIN
- What a mess.
- This is driving me crazy.
It really is Kian's Bizarre B&B.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B
SHE FINDS SOMETHING
Hey, we got a hose. Here.
- The hose is here?
- Yeah.
A HOSE IS BROUGHT IN
Thank you!
Gosh.
My goodness.
WATER FOR DISHWASHING SECURED
Let's use it. But wait…
ANOTHER
PROBLEM?
Why are you wearing my dad's underwear?
Your dad's?
Yeah, it's the same as my dad's.
Did your dad
buy them online?
I don't know. They're similar.
Kian, there won't be
any more guests, right?
I don't think any more will come.
We can't accept any more now.
We can't handle it.
What do we do?
What?
THE PHONE'S RINGING?
- No!
- You're getting another call?
- They're here?
- We have more?
MORE GUESTS?
THERE ARE ALREADY SIX ON THE FIRST DAY
- Hello?
Hello, I'm Lee Jun-ho,
and I'm checking in today.
Yes, hello.
A GUEST NAMED LEE JUN-HO?
How many of you are there?
- I'm by myself.
- By yourself?
I'll send you the address.
You can find the place with GPS.
Okay, thank you.
- Bye.
How many do we have in total?
Including us, two, four, six…
Eleven people.
What's your name?
My name is Woo Jae-eun.
- Woo Jae-eun.
- Yes.
- And you?
- Kim Hee-jeong.
Kim Hee-jeong.
Yoo Don-hee.
Seo Jeong-won.
THE BOSS IS IN CHARGE
OF COMMUNICATION WITH GUESTS
Just "S," not "Su."
- Smi…
- Smita.
Snehal.
Are you sisters?
- Yes.
- Sisters? You are sisters.
- Right?
- Yes.
OLDER TWIN, YOUNGER TWIN
"Jae-eun."
SHARING GUESTS' NAMES WITH THE EMPLOYEES
- Someone else is coming.
- What?
My goodness.
FOURTH GUEST GROUP IS APPROACHING
4:40 P.M.
Incredible.
Hello?
- Hello.
Hello.
LEE JUN-HO
- Hello.
- It's hard to open, isn't it?
Hello.
- Hello.
He kind of looks like a Shaolin monk.
He must be a monk.
I'm Lee Jun-ho, one of your guests today.
PUTTING HIS HANDS TOGETHER?
Are you a monk?
No, I'm not a monk.
You're not a monk? I'm sorry.
I'm not a monk,
but I do study and teach Buddhism.
I see.
Hello.
I practice Sunmudo at Golgulsa Temple.
I'm Lee Jun-ho,
or Dharma Teacher Hyeonung.
ALL GUESTS FOR DAY 1 HAVE CHECKED IN
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hello, it's nice to meet you.
So,
for your room…
Yes?
- There's one.
- The floor.
Is it for one person?
You can sleep out here.
YOU CAN USE THIS AREA
Or you can use this room.
- Here?
- Yes, just think of it
as making yourself at home
at your friend's house.
Then, I'll sleep in this room.
THE GUESTS' ROOMS HAVE ALL BEEN DECIDED
5:00 P.M.
Shall we have dinner at 5:45 p.m.?
DINNERTIME
5:45 P.M.
- Zuha.
- Yes?
I think I need you to be my assistant.
Could you help me?
HEAD CHEF YEON-KOUNG & SOUS-CHEF KAZUHA
TODAY'S DINNER:
PORK BELLY KIMCHI FRIED RICE
- Cut some Spam for me.
- Okay.
But I don't think
our Indian guests can eat that.
They can't eat pork, right?
- Our Indians guests?
- Really?
Spam's made of pork.
We should ask them.
Is there anyone who can't eat meat?
Do you two eat meat?
We don't eat beef.
Aside from beef, is pork or ham okay?
- It's okay.
- Spam!
Okay, got it. Just no beef then.
Pork is okay.
Is that so? That's a relief.
It is.
It's a good thing we bought pork.
That was very sharp of them.
If I want to cut the Spam into tiny bits…
- Okay.
- Should I cut it like this?
Just chop it up.
Don't worry about the shape.
- Really?
- I will make it delicious. Don't worry.
We have to chop this up.
Is this right?
- Are you doing all right?
- Yes.
They can be smaller.
- Smaller?
- Yeah, you can make them very small.
Smaller.
THE COACH DIRECTS THE DINNER
I'm on it.
We have to grill the pork belly too.
THINGS ARE GOING SMOOTHLY
ROLLING UP HER PANTS
Goodness.
STARTING TO STIR-FRY KIMCHI
SORRY, BUT CAN YOU PASS ME THE SPAM
- Spam?
- Yeah.
THANK YOU
Gosh, that smells great.
PUTTING IN THE SPAM THAT ZUHA CUT
That looks so good.
ADDING THE RICE THE BOSS MADE
What do you think, Kazuha?
- It looks delicious.
- Right?
This looks amazing.
KIMCHI FRIED RICE IS READY
Hey, look at that.
LAUNDRY BASKET
TRAMPOLINE
- That's really fun.
- Right.
- Want to do it together?
- Want to jump together?
- Sure.
- Shall we try?
- Let's do it!
- Sure.
Let's do it!
- One, two, three.
- They're having a blast.
- They're adorable.
They're really enjoying themselves.
One, two, three!
A POPULAR SPOT AMONG THE GUESTS
Goodness.
How big should I cut them?
Like the pieces of grilled eel
on rice bowls.
Like donburi.
EASY-TO-UNDERSTAND INSTRUCTIONS
You should flip the meat, Kazuha.
Yeah, flip them now or they'll burn.
They might burn it.
IT DID BURN
I'll grow and get better.
YOU'RE SO CUTE, KAZUHA
SHE TAKES OUT THE WELL-COOKED PORK BELLY
AND FRIES EGGS TOO
This first?
Once we put those on top, we're done.
It looks so good.
- It looks so good.
- Right?
PORK BELLY KIMCHI FRIED RICE IS READY
Hey, these…
We'll need a box to lower these.
THEY HAVE TO GET DINNER DOWN
A LONG WAY DOWN
- What?
- Look.
We should help them lower it.
- Hey…
- Could you help us?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
I'll go midway, and you…
You know what I mean?
If you hand them to me…
- Here.
- Is there food inside?
- Yeah, be careful.
- Okay.
A KIAN'S B&B-STYLE FOOD DELIVERY
We'll just need spoons.
This looks so good!
Oh, my gosh.
This looks great.
Everyone, come eat!
DINNERTIME
The dinner…
VOICE CRACKING
Kazuha and Yeon-koung cooked the dinner.
Please enjoy the food.
YEON-KOUNG & KAZUHA'S
PORK BELLY KIMCHI FRIED RICE
- Hand them out.
- For you two.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- All right, for you two.
- Thank you.
Hey, I like Spam,
and it even has pork belly.
Right? Me too.
Why does this feel like a temple meal?
- Thank you.
- Hello.
Hello.
If we eat together here,
it'll feel like a temple meal.
- "Temple meal."
- It does feel like that.
But it was like this too in Season 1.
It felt like being in a temple.
But it's not a templestay. Just…
Just imagine you're at a friend's house
and eat comfortably.
I hope you enjoy your food.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you for the food.
THEIR FIRST DINNER IN KIAN'S B&B
I wonder if it tastes all right.
CURIOUS TO SEE THEIR REACTIONS
I do feel a bit of pressure
since we made the food.
- It feels like we're being judged.
- Right? It feels like that.
Does it taste all right?
Yeah. It's good.
RELIEVED
Right?
Is it good?
It's so good.
It's delicious.
- The fried egg. You did great.
- Really?
Have some more kimchi.
- Okay.
KIMCHI
DROPPED KIMCHI
You dropped some.
Goodness.
YUM
I dropped that though.
I'm sorry.
I hear the four of you are 20.
4 COLLEGE FRESHMEN
What are your majors?
WOO JAE-EUN, KIM HEE-JEONG
DANCE MAJORS
YOO DON-HEE
FASHION MAJOR
SEO JEONG-WON
ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING MAJOR
You're at an ambitious age.
What kind of martial art?
It's called Sunmudo. Monks practice it.
SUNMUDO INSTRUCTOR
Sunmudo?
- How old are you?
- I'm 37.
- You're 37?
- Yes.
You look so young.
What do you two do?
YOUNGER TWIN: MODEL
OLDER TWIN: GLOBAL MARKETER
That's so cool.
Not at all. It just ended up like that.
She's also modest.
I see.
How old are you?
We were born in 1998.
- You're 28?
- Yes.
I'm ten years older.
I was born in 1988.
You're an athlete!
- What?
- You're an athlete.
- Me?
- A badminton player, right?
Yes, a badminton player.
SO YOU ARE A BADMINTON PLAYER
How did you know?
Yes, I'm a badminton player.
I GOT IT RIGHT
Badminton? Right.
She's a famous badminton player.
You're his fans, right?
YES
- Your acting!
- Seriously.
It's so good.
Thank you so much.
So you like him better
as an actor than as a singer?
They may not know he sings.
- We do.
- You do?
SHINee.
What?
We know.
WE ARE SHINEE
Right, he's a member of SHINee.
I'm a member of 2PM.
And I'm a volleyball player,
not badminton.
Oh, no.
We should stop talking.
Is anyone up for the sauna today?
- Sauna.
- Us.
- Want to use the sauna?
- Yes.
Should we do it too?
Then, we'll open the sauna today.
And are you okay
with lights-out at 11:00 p.m.?
Yes.
The reason is the lights…
Everyone, this whole space is one room.
AS THEY KNOW, IT'S ONE ROOM
So it all turns off.
EVENING SCHEDULE ON DAY 1
8:00 P.M. SAUNA OPENS
11:00 P.M. LIGHTS OUT
The sky's so beautiful.
- It's insane.
- The sunset.
The sky's so pretty tonight.
You're right.
I want to go out.
I want to go outside.
- Sure, you can go out.
- Go ahead. We'll clean up.
You can put your bowls there.
We'll put them up.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I really enjoyed the food.
- Thank you.
We just put them here?
We'll go up.
Can you take the bowls from them?
Okay.
Hey, you should hurry and go out.
The sky's so pretty right now.
Just put them down and go.
- Want to go out?
- Yes.
- We will.
- Let's go.
KIAN'S B&B
LET'S GO OUT
Hey, look.
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful.
It's prettier in the evening.
THE SKY REDDENS ABOVE DAEGWALLYEONG
KIAN'S B&B
LIGHTS ARE ON AT KIAN'S B&B AS WELL
It's so beautiful.
Look at the sky.
The color is insane.
It's so pretty.
Why is it so pretty?
Look.
The sky is…
- Beautiful.
- Is it romantic?
Gosh, this is so…
6:30 P.M.
It's on its way down.
The sky's insane today.
AFTER A SHORT ROMANTIC MOMENT
DELIVERING DISHES TO WASH
You're doing the dishes?
I'll do it.
THE BOSS AND ZUHA DO THE DISHES
There's no time to look at my phone.
Are these washed or not?
You can't leave these like this.
Why not?
BACK INTO THE GREASY WATER
No, you have to wash them right.
DISHWASHING COACH APPEARS
- What?
- Did you wash these?
Aren't they clean?
Did you really wash them?
Should I wash them again?
- You cleaned them?
- Yeah.
- Did you really wash it?
- I did.
Hey, you can tell
once you rinse them.
Did you even wash these?
Why do you doubt my dishwashing?
They're clean.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
If it's only for yourself, it's okay.
- But make it clean for everyone. Okay?
- I'm being very careful.
- Of course.
- Okay.
RUNNING OFF
HE PUTS THE CLEANED DISHES AWAY
AND YEON-KOUNG FINISHES THE REST
JUN-HO JOINS THEM
It's so heavy.
It's quite heavy.
Right?
CLEAN
Nice job.
DISHWASHING AFTER DINNER IS FINISHED
I'll just wring this out.
We just need to decide
on tomorrow's dinner.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
Aren't you making okonomiyaki?
- What?
- Is that so?
Didn't Kazuha say she'd make okonomiyaki?
Okay, I'll do it.
- Tomorrow?
- Yes, tomorrow?
Okay. Good work, everyone.
THE GUESTS UNPACK
WHILE THE EMPLOYEES ZONE OUT
All three of us are…
What are you doing there?
I don't think I can come down.
He's exhausted.
WHAT THEY DID TODAY
OPEN THE BIGGEST DOOR EVER
5 TIMES
- Open.
Pull. It's open.
Hold on!
CLOSE THE BIG DOOR 5 TIMES
CLIMB THE DISHRAG 23 TIMES
Hold on, my toes hurt.
Geez.
WASH A LOT OF DISHES
Jun-ho.
Today's only the first day. Remember that.
Still, a day has passed.
It hasn't yet.
Not yet.
Right now,
- it doesn't feel real.
- Right?
It feels…
It's like a dream. You feel dazed.
THE BOSS IS EXHAUSTED TOO
Geez.
Your nose must be still running.
I'll be better in there.
- Where? Sauna?
- The sauna.
Should we just open the sauna now?
Those who want to can do it now.
It's hot.
I should go collect some water.
Here? I see. It is.
I bet we'll sleep well after the sauna.
I know. We're actually already sleepy.
Right.
It'll be so steamy.
They pour the water on that.
THE SAUNA IS READY
I think it's ready.
CURRENT TEMPERATURE: 60°C
Oh, my gosh.
OPENS RIGHT AWAY
Please enjoy.
Should we go?
HESITANT
Everyone, you're at a friend's house.
Make yourselves at home.
You should get changed.
GETTING CHANGED INTO SAUNA CLOTHES
- It's cold.
THIS IS WHEN YOU NEED A SAUNA
Hold on.
How do you do this?
I've always wanted to try.
GUEST JUN-HO JOINS
SATISFACTION LEVEL HIGH
CONTENT
MORE GUESTS JOIN
Oh, my gosh.
Do you know this?
- Sheep heads?
- Right, the sheep heads.
I think you have to roll it
like this first.
- Do you remember now?
- Yes.
It worked.
Like this?
That's it.
It looks good on you.
Should I do bleat?
It's so cute!
PROUD
They love it.
- Isn't this what you wanted?
- It is.
We should join them.
JUN-HO GETS CHANGED FIRST
JUN-HO ENTERS
Why did you want to keep me out?
Come in.
I need to warm up.
Let's give it a go.
Someone's coming in.
THE BOSS JOINS TOO
Hey, there.
Welcome.
- This is nice.
- Seriously, it's so good.
YEON-KOUNG TAKES A SHOWER
AND SO DOES ZUHA
When you first came into the house,
you were surprised, weren't you?
Yes.
- From afar…
- It looked small.
- Small, right?
- Yes.
It looked so small,
but it slowly got bigger.
- Yeah, for real.
- It slowly got bigger.
We felt the same.
When we first saw it from afar,
it looked smaller
than we thought it would be.
But it was huge up close.
I was shocked.
But I have a question.
In Season 1,
entering the house was the toughest part.
I'm going to lose my mind. This is…
IT'S NOT EASY TO ENTER KIAN'S B&B
Did you not want the guests to come in?
No, I made it that way
because it makes people
talk to each other more.
Going in and out.
I found that it helps strangers get close.
IT FORCES THEM TO GET CLOSE
- You're right.
- Good idea.
- Right?
- Seriously.
- Where's your hometown?
- Busan.
- Busan?
- Yes.
I lived in Busan until I joined a temple
in Gyeongju when I was 14.
Did you want to become a monk?
Actually, I was a monk about 15 years ago.
- Really?
- Yes, I entered the temple then.
While studying Buddhism, I thought
I needed more real-world experience,
so I told the senior monk.
And now, I'm a Sunmudo instructor
and a Dharma Teacher.
That's fascinating.
Then, do you drink?
I do all those fun things
in the material world,
and when things get hard,
I go to the temple and purify myself.
I can never leave the material world.
I'm attached to so many things.
No, I'm also in the middle
between the material world and Buddhism
and living my life the best I can.
I should pray to the Buddha
before I go to bed tonight.
Right.
Buddha, please guide us
to do this well without any trouble.
It's too hot.
ESCAPING THE SAUNA
It's too hot. I'm dying.
Yes, you can have beer if you want.
BOSS ESCAPES SAUNA TOO
I sweated it all out. It's so hot.
SOAKED
GIANT SOCK
RUSTLING
Will it fit me?
RIGHT IN
This is so nice.
I should memorize their names.
Smita.
Snehal.
Mita and Nehal.
Nehal.
Like, "You do your job."
"Mita, you do your job."
Geez, I have a terrible memory now.
YEON-KOUNG COMES OUT AFTER A SHOWER
AFTER PUTTING ON NEW SOCKS
SHE SEES THE BOSS LYING DOWN
- Boss.
- Yes?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm tired.
But aren't you all sweaty right now?
I didn't sweat much.
You still sweated.
Just a little.
You shouldn't be lying there
after sweating.
Why not? I'm fine with it.
- Really?
- Why not?
You sweat, so bad stuff came out
of your body and into your bed.
You're going to sleep in that
after your shower?
I'll just sleep with the bad stuff.
SHE GIVES UP
- Did you wash up?
- Yes.
- Feels nice, doesn't it?
Want a snack? How about a beer?
Shall we have a drink?
Kazuha, you look so cute.
You look cute after washing up.
ZUHA JOINS
- It's been great meeting you. Cheers.
- Cheers.
- It's been nice meeting you.
- He's 20.
- They're 20?
Yeah, freshmen.
They're starting college.
That's amazing.
You must have a lot of free time now.
- That's right.
- Right? You just got in.
When do you start?
- Next Thursday.
- We're here for three days.
I'm staying for five days.
Really?
GUEST JUN-HO
5 DAYS, 4 NIGHTS
SNEHAL, SMITA
4 DAYS, 3 NIGHTS
HEE-JEONG, JAE-EUN
3 DAYS, 2 NIGHTS
I hope it'll be
a great experience for you.
GLANCING
GLANCING AGAIN
TARGET LOCKED ON
Hey, is there…
someone you like over there?
THERE IS SOMEONE HE LIKES IN THE SAUNA?
No, there isn't.
He keeps looking over that way.
Don-hee was looking.
That's possible.
Just tell us,
and we'll hook you up.
Yeah, she'll help you two get together.
I wanted to go running tomorrow.
- What?
- I saw there was a running trail here.
Running? Really?
I wanted to take a lap.
RUNNING TRAIL
FROM RUNNING BEGINNERS TO FANATICS
EVERYONE CAN ENJOY IT TOGETHER
THE RUNNING TRAIL PROVIDED BY KIAN'S B&B
Kian84 runs marathons often.
- I thought we'd do it together.
- But he's sick now.
- Right, I know.
- He's not feeling well.
Then, let's not tell him.
- Okay.
- No, you should.
But…
He's not feeling well, so we shouldn't.
He'll say no if he doesn't want to.
That is true.
Yeah, so just tell him
that you want to run with him.
THE BOSS GETS UP
HE GOES TO TAKE A SHOWER
Boss, did you wash up?
HYGIENE SUPERVISOR OF KIAN'S B&B
I did.
- Is that water or sweat?
- He didn't.
You keep asking what I did.
So did you wash up or not?
I washed very thoroughly.
- Really? So you showered?
- Yeah.
Should I do it again?
Because he was sweating earlier
- after being in the sauna.
- Right.
And he looks exactly the same now.
- Only his clothes changed.
- Yeah.
I hope Boss gets better.
Hang in there, Boss.
Shouldn't you have some medicine?
Well, I feel better after the sauna.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'll put it here.
HE HANGS HIS SAUNA CLOTHES
SOAKED IN SWEAT TO DRY
I guess you don't drink much.
AND JOINS THEM
- Aren't you pushing yourself too hard?
- Are you okay?
I'm fine.
- Really?
- That's good.
They just said it's their dream
to go running with you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Do you think you can?
Let's run together tomorrow.
HE EAGERLY SAYS YES
Maybe we can go run at around 8:00 a.m.?
Sounds great.
EVERYONE'S FREE TO JOIN THE RUN
Gosh.
I FORGOT TO WASH MY FACE
CHECKING HIS APPEARANCE
I just saw something terrible.
SOMETHING TERRIBLE?
You didn't change your underwear?
UNDERWEAR
I didn't.
CULTURE SHOCK
I just happened to see it.
BEFORE SHOWER, AFTER SHOWER
Leave my hygiene alone.
But you were sweaty.
- Sweaty?
- Yeah.
I'm going to sweat again anyway.
Yeon-koung likes to observe people.
She was worried and told me
to wash my sweat-soaked underwear.
Boss, did you wash up?
Did you brush your teeth?
And change your underwear.
Yeon-koung's quite funny.
She's funny.
I don't think it'll kill me.
We can withstand that much bacteria.
He's a real man.
SHE CAN'T UNDERSTAND
Anyway, if you want to join me
in this campaign
of not changing underwear,
come and whisper to me,
"I didn't change it today."
Everyone, it's 11:00 p.m.
It's time to go to bed.
So get ready.
What is it?
Aren't we sleeping on this?
- Let's just sleep here.
- Okay.
THEY CHOOSE THE SPACIOUS FLOOR
Want to use another comforter
or just share this one?
Let's use another so we each have one.
This one looks good.
- This one's nice.
- This one?
SCARED
JEONG-WON AND DON-HEE'S BEDS ARE SET
THE BOSS IS GETTING READY TO SLEEP TOO
It was my dream to watch
your game in person, but I couldn't.
What? Why didn't you come?
Hurry up.
Just a second.
GIGGLING
Why were you laughing?
- What?
- Why were you laughing?
They're cute. They laugh a lot.
Did you brush your teeth?
I did.
Why do you keep…
Why do you keep asking me about stuff,
like dishwashing, underwear, and my teeth?
I brushed them so hard
I almost ground them down.
Good job.
Yeah, thanks.
I'll do it again if you want.
No. You did well.
Gosh, I'm dying.
Geez, who made this?
- Good night.
That's so cute!
GOOD NIGHT
- Good night, Boss.
- Good night.
- Good job today.
Hey, the lights…
WE NEED TO TURN THE LIGHTS OFF
NEXT TO THE DOOR HANDLE
SWITCHES ARE ABOUT 3.5 M HIGH
KITCHEN, LIVING ROOM
Let's turn it off with a ball.
With a ball?
Let's try.
Wait, how do you hit this properly?
You want to do it?
Let's both try it.
This hurts my wrist.
It's difficult.
You're so close.
I think it'll work.
- It's not working.
- Geez.
It worked.
Geez.
There's one left to turn off.
I think Yeon-koung needs to do this.
WE NEED YEON-KOUNG
Cool.
Should I do it?
- Show us!
- Show us, Yeon-koung.
KITCHEN LIGHT IS YEON-KOUNG'S JOB
FLICKERING
I'll have to hit it hard.
- Harder?
- Or it won't turn off.
Is that it?
You're so cool.
You have to hit it hard.
You need to hit it hard.
Good night, everyone!
LIGHTS OUT
This is so fun.
- We have two more days.
- Right.
ZUHA GETS INTO THE COMFORTER TOO
- Good night!
- Good night.
THE BOSS'S SNEEZING CONTINUES
DEEP INTO THE NIGHT
KIAN'S B&B
DAY 2
IT'S SUNNY TODAY
THE SNOW IS MELTING
7:00 A.M.
HANGER & LIVING ROOM
FRIDGE
RAMYEON BOXES
TV CABINET
JUN-HO WAKES UP
BOWING
JEONG-WON AND DON-HEE WAKE UP EARLY
- You weren't cold?
- No.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes. It was actually hot.
AFTER CHECKING ON THE GUESTS,
HE GOES TO WASH UP
THE BOSS IS STILL ASLEEP
If no one else wakes up,
should we go running by ourselves?
Okay.
THEY HOPE TO GO RUNNING AT 8:00 A.M.
Let's play omok.
THEY WILL PLAY OMOK WHILE WAITING
GO STONES & BOARD
HE WALKS CAREFULLY NOT TO WAKE OTHERS UP
The air is cold.
SURPRISED
Gosh, the air is cold.
QUIET AGAIN
He's sleep-talking.
Geez, it's cold.
Good morning.
Hey, aren't you cold?
We were warm.
THE ONLY ONE THAT FEELS COLD
HE TAKES A SOCK OUT
Gosh, it's cold.
7:30 A.M.
YEON-KOUNG WAKES UP
SHE MAKES HER BED RIGHT AWAY
IT'S NOT EASY TO GET OUT OF THE ROOM
Damn it.
Geez, what a pain.
7:55 A.M.
It's 8:00 a.m.
IT'S TIME TO GO RUNNING, BUT IT'S QUIET
Don-hee, should we go?
THE TWO PLAN TO GO RUN BY THEMSELVES
Did you sleep well?
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
- Going out? Let's go.
Yes!
RUNNING PARTICIPANTS
JUN-HO ALSO WAKES UP TO RUN
Shouldn't we wake Kian up?
HE PROMISED TO RUN WITH THEM
BUT IS STILL ASLEEP
Wake him up.
Wake him up?
Kian, we're ready to go running.
Already?
We were waiting.
Gosh.
SNEEZING
Are you all right, Boss?
I'm so cold.
HE STILL FEELS LETHARGIC
You promised, so you have to go.
PRINCIPLED YEON-KOUNG
Let's go.
AS YEON-KOUNG SAID, HE KEEPS HIS PROMISE
Hey, you acted like you wouldn't run,
but you woke up early.
Come on, I used to be an athlete.
This is nothing.
I should at least be this diligent.
That's good.
EATS A SNACK
We have to open the door.
Push it open.
OPENING THE DOOR ON TIPTOE
Wait, you can reach it?
Of course.
You can reach it like this?
IT'S EASIER WHEN PUSHING IT OPEN
The weather is nice.
So this place looks like this.
- Let's go.
- Sure, let's go.
Are we starting from here?
Apparently, we might see cows on the way.
- Really?
- Yeah, they let their cows graze here.
Really?
THEY MIGHT RUN INTO COWS
Running on a snowy path…
- It's romantic.
- Right.
It's so exciting to run on a snowy path.
- Are you excited?
- Yes.
You find this exciting?
- It's exciting!
- It's exciting.
Yeon-koung asked, so I went running.
It did feel nice to get some fresh air.
I was always busy
playing volleyball in the winter,
so I never got to enjoy any winter sports.
I knew I wouldn't experience
something like this anywhere else.
It was like a dream
on my bucket list came true.
It was snowy everywhere,
and with all those hills,
it looked like
a beautiful scene from a fairy tale.
It's uphill.
Oh, no.
- Hold on.
- Geez.
This is so…
Again?
THE HILL GETS STEEPER
What's up with this hill?
How do we go up this?
This uphill is too tough.
I'll put the B&B on flat land next time.
I'm so tired.
MORNING RUN ENDS
- Good work, everyone.
- Good work.
Good job, everyone.
Good job.
Good work.
LET'S CLOSE THE DOOR
Damn it.
IT'S HARDER WHEN CLOSING IT
- You can just…
- I'll hold you.
You don't have to.
- You can just…
- Okay.
HE LEARNED HOW TO CLOSE IT BY DAY 2
How do you close it?
You can reach it?
Like this.
Gosh, you…
Hey.
Pull it more or it'll open.
I think it's enough.
Okay.
I'm so tired.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
SNEEZING
I feel dizzy.
Boss, are you okay?
I don't think I can move.
I'm exhausted.
OUT OF ENERGY AFTER RUN
YEON-KOUNG WORKS OUT SOME MORE
- Hi, Jun-ho. Did you sleep well?
- What about you?
We went out to run.
I know. And you're on the bike
after running?
- We only did one lap.
- Really?
- The uphill…
- It was too steep?
Yeah.
And you're working out more inside.
WORKING HARD
SHE FINISHES THE 30-MIN WORKOUT
GETTING READY FOR WORK
THE YOUNGEST WAKES UP
CRAWLING
GETTING READY FOR WORK
THE BOSS WAKES UP AGAIN
It's cold.
RUBBING THE SLEEP FROM HIS EYES
THE BOSS WASHES UP TOO
DROPS ON THE FLOOR
WHILE OTHERS GOT READY FOR WORK
JUN-HO PREPARED SOME FRUIT
- Have some of these.
- We can eat these?
- You can.
- Do we get breakfast too?
- Do you like strawberries? And grapes?
- Yes.
Shine Muscats.
So you four will go
everywhere together today?
- Yes.
- And come back together?
Our plans were the same.
- Right.
- That's perfect.
You'll become a lot closer.
- Be safe.
- Okay.
- What about the tops?
- Give them to me.
- Thank you.
- I'll take them.
Thank you.
STRAWBERRY TOPS IN HIS HANDS
- I'll take your waste.
- Thank you.
It's an honor.
- Have a safe trip.
- Okay.
SWEET JUN-HO
- What time will you be back?
- Around 5:00 p.m.
- At 5:00 p.m.? Have a safe trip.
- Okay.
- See you later.
- Have fun.
GUEST JUN-HO
SMITA, SNEHAL
EVERYONE'S GONE ON THEIR TRIPS
- Everyone left?
- Yeah.
KIAN'S B&B IS EMPTY NOW
Did you sleep well? Do you feel sick?
I was cold.
We should clean up in a bit.
10:30 A.M.
Okay, we have until 5:00 p.m.,
and what we have to do is clean.
Clean.
And we should prepare
for unexpected guests.
Tell me what we need.
- I'll go by myself and…
- Alone?
I'll buy everything really fast.
- Then, I'll clean up.
- Okay. I won't take long.
- I'll be back.
- Bye.
- Jun-ho.
- Yes?
Have lunch while you're out.
Lunch?
It's 10:30 a.m.,
so won't you be back at lunchtime?
Let's eat together.
Okay. I'm actually hungry.
You are?
I should eat some snacks.
You can eat. I'm all right.
Okay.
KIAN'S B&B
- Let's clean.
- Yes, Boss.
CLEANING BEGINS
Gosh, it's dusty.
Geez, the house is…
The house's too big.
It is pretty dirty.
- There's a lot of dust.
- There is.
After doing this,
if we use a lint roller, it'll be clean.
Okay.
THE YOUNGEST SWEEPS THE FLOOR
YEON-KOUNG REMOVES DUST
WITH A LINT ROLLER
AND THE BOSS CLEANS EVERY CORNER
- I think…
- Yeah?
- The entrance should always be clean.
- Right.
So we should clean it.
DIRTY
Want to dust the mat?
- How?
- We'll bring it outside.
BY THE WAY THE ENTRANCE MAT IS
HUGE LIKE KIAN'S B&B
1 YEON-KOUNG
1.5 YEON-KOUNG
Okay.
Okay, take it out.
Bring it out.
Geez.
Zuha, go and bring it out.
- The mop.
A MOP TO DUST A MAT OFF?
- You hit it.
- Hit it with that.
- Okay.
- The opposite side.
- Like this?
- Yeah, hit it with that.
Like this?
Hit it.
- There you go.
- No!
- Hit it like this.
- How? Like this?
LIKE THIS?
No.
No? What's wrong?
Hit with the side of the handle.
Hit the mat with the side, not the tip.
SIDE? TIP?
How do you do that?
- Make the dust shake off.
- Make it shake off.
Harder.
You hold this.
SUBSTITUTION
What's the difference?
One, two, three.
- I'll hit hard.
- Okay.
- Slant it a bit.
- Slant it?
NOT THAT DIFFERENT
What on earth?
STILL DUSTY
- Geez.
- It's not working.
Flip it.
Flip it?
Lift it and flip it.
We did flip it.
No, like this.
Switch.
- Switch.
- Slant it.
Okay, pull on it more.
The dust is coming off.
- Right.
- It's working.
Hit harder.
HIT THE BOSS HARD
Geez.
I think it's enough.
- It's enough.
- Let's go.
Good work.
THEY FINISH DUSTING THE MAT
Okay.
It's clean.
All right.
THE DOOR
NEEDS TO BE
CLOSED AGAIN
Let's keep it open.
Let's keep it open for a bit.
VENTILATING
Hey, we should wipe down
all the slippers with wet wipes.
The bottoms.
The bottoms of the slippers?
Yes.
Let's use a rag. Wet wipes are a waste.
A rag? Okay.
WASHING A RAG TO USE INSTEAD OF WET WIPES
HE CLEANS THE SINK WHILE HE'S AT IT
WASHES HIS FACE
AND TIDIES HIS SIDEBURNS
Use a rag.
We'll clean these
since we cleaned the house.
WITH ONE RAG
WIPING VIGOROUSLY
What?
- What on earth is this?
- What?
What's with this show?
This show?
It's like a cleaning show.
I just had reality hit me hard
while cleaning these slippers like this.
Hey, you can't come back
even if you want to.
Every day is so precious.
I mean, what on earth are we doing?
Hopes and dreams.
Geez.
KIAN'S B&B OF HOPE AND DREAMS
When we have new guests come in,
we should put their suitcases there
and use these rags.
- Wipe them? Okay.
- Let's wipe the wheels before they enter.
We should wipe them down.
Then, it'll be cleaner here.
KIAN'S B&B RULES
CLEAN GUESTS' SUITCASES WHEN THEY COME
Let's wrap up.
Let's tidy this up first.
Geez.
What on earth?
Boss, what's this?
What is it?
What?
THE SLIPPERS GOT DIRTY
He's driving me crazy.
THE CULPRIT
Are you serious? We just cleaned them.
Sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
10 MINUTES EARLIER
Let's take them all.
HE WENT TO THE STORAGE
IN THE SLIPPERS
I'm sorry. I should've set an example.
I'm sorry.
Clean those slippers later.
Okay.
Aren't you hungry?
- What?
- I'm hungry.
It's lunchtime.
12:30 P.M.
It is.
Let's eat first.
Yeah, we should.
I'm hungry.
What do we eat?
Ramyeon and leftover rice?
- I think that's better.
- Right.
I'll ask Jun-ho where he is,
so we can eat together.
Where are you?
I'm almost there.
Hurry up. We're making the ramyeon now.
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Go ahead and eat first.
Okay.
I'll add a bit of kimchi.
ADDING KIMCHI TO RAMYEON BROTH
ONE MORE TIME
Ham?
ADDING HAM BROKEN UP BY SCISSORS
This is going to be so good.
It does look good.
Shall we dig in?
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
It's good. You cooked it really well.
You don't gain much weight, right?
I do if I eat a lot.
I need to watch my diet.
Really?
When I was an athlete,
I didn't eat unhealthy stuff,
like fried food or flour-based food.
And as soon as I retired,
I ate a ton of it for over a month.
I ate everything I wanted to eat.
I even drank every day.
Then, when I got a checkup,
they said I had high cholesterol.
- You?
- Really?
And a high liver somatic index.
- Right away.
It happened in just two months.
So, I decided to get it together.
- So I do it every day.
- Work out?
Even just a little bit.
- Yeah.
Exercising?
By the way, I saw the scenery
after running.
- It was amazing.
- Beautiful?
It really was.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
We should go check that out.
The river. Right.
It's frozen, so I think it'll be fun.
With the sled.
- Right.
- The ice sled.
I've never done it before.
- Never? Ice sleds?
- No.
THE LAKE SURROUNDING KIAN'S B&B
TODAY'S EVENT FOR KIAN'S B&B
RIDING THE ICE SLEDS
Gosh.
JUN-HO IS BACK FROM GROCERY SHOPPING
HIS HANDS ARE FULL
Right, the coffee.
Okay.
Welcome back. Come on up.
Come eat ramyeon.
- Welcome back.
- He's here.
Here.
Thanks.
Good job.
Should I add rice?
- Add it?
- Yeah. I think that's better.
- Let's do it.
- It'll be better.
- It is good.
- Yeah.
Ramyeon tastes the best
in places like this.
- Right?
- Yeah.
It's good.
Later, when they come back
at around 5:00 p.m.,
we're going to go ride
the ice sled at the river.
- That sounds good.
- Together.
This is delicious.
1:00 P.M.
Hey, let's take a break.
I'm sleepy.
You're sleeping right away?
I'll just lie down for a bit.
Why do I like lying down so much?
Maybe my time's coming?
I'm lying down so often.
Hey, your runny nose
has improved from yesterday.
- It stopped running.
- That's good.
Yeah. You got better.
TIME TO SLEEP
God, it's so cold.
THEY DIDN'T CLOSE THE DOOR EARLIER
THE SHOES THEY TOOK OUTSIDE EARLIER
HE BRINGS THE SHOES IN
BEFORE HE GOES TO SLEEP
Boss wants to rest, but he can't.
Kian, do we have any tape?
- Tape?
- Yes.
I have to go to the storage.
HE VISITS THE STORAGE
BEFORE HE GOES TO SLEEP
It's not here.
HE CLOSES THE DOOR BEFORE HE GOES TO SLEEP
HE CLIMBS THE SOFA BEFORE HE GOES TO SLEEP
I'm so tired.
Are you okay?
Gosh.
WHILE THE BOSS IS TAKING A REST
We have to clean the bathroom.
THE EMPLOYEES FINISH UP THE CLEANING
CLEANING THE BATHROOM
CLEANING THE SAUNA
AND JUN-HO DOES THE DISHES
They said they'd be back around 5:00 p.m.
What about us?
It's already 2:00 p.m.
We have three hours left.
Before I went to sleep last night,
I watched your "SPAGHETTI" video.
You did? Gosh.
You looked totally different.
- Really?
- Seriously.
You're a flirt on stage.
Like this. What is that?
A DIFFERENT SIDE OF THE YOUNGEST
It wasn't the Kazuha I knew.
Like this.
I was shocked.
You're good at that.
- Right?
- She is.
You're good.
How you are in everyday life
is also a totally different
from when you're playing on the court.
Of course.
I can fool around like this here.
But over there,
I was a professional.
- Right.
- It's different.
All of your younger colleagues
must be scared of you now.
Do they act awkward or scared?
I think both.
I thought I'd be too.
- What?
- But I was surprised you were so kind.
Really? Do I look kind of cold?
Rather than cold…
- Fierce? Right.
- You have that fierce presence.
Really? It must be
because I'm always yelling.
Normally, I'm not like that though.
We have free time right now.
- Should we go somewhere?
- Should we?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Where are you going?
Gosh, weren't you sleeping?
Well…
It'd be nice to go check out Sky Ranch
or one of those places.
SKY RANCH
It's only 22 minutes from here.
It's nearby.
- What do you say?
- Sounds good.
- Want to go?
- Yeah.
Let's go then. It won't take long.
Why do I feel so weak?
You'll feel better once you go.
Let's go.
Let's go, Kian.
- You're driving, Jun-ho?
- Yes.
SKY RANCH
It's nice to go somewhere like this.
Yeah, I didn't think
we'd have time for something like this.
This is nice.
Did Jae-eun's pair
and Don-hee's pair go separately?
- No, the four of them went together.
- Together.
I hope something happens between them.
- Yeah.
- You can't help but smile at them.
Yeah.
ANMOKHAEBYEON BEACH
- It's the ocean!
THE 20-YEAR-OLDS' TRIP
- It's emerald.
- This will be so fun.
SKY BIKE
- It's a round-trip?
- It seems so.
I'm going!
I'm so scared! Oh, no!
Hey, this is fun!
Let's go!
Here goes nothing!
- Hey!
- Let's go!
- It's so beautiful.
- This is so romantic.
Let's go!
- Didn't the ocean look so beautiful?
- Yeah, it did.
Don't you want to go in?
Let's do it.
ANMOKHAEBYEON BEACH
We can't go in, Don-hee! It's so cold.
Hey, it's so cold. It's no joke.
It's so cold.
Hey, rock, paper, scissors
and loser carries the winner?
- Sure.
- Let's do it.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
LOSER: DON-HEE
WINNER: HEE-JEONG
Okay! Go!
Let's go!
My feet hurt so much.
- Just bear it.
- You can hold on tight.
Okay.
- My feet hurt so much!
- Go up to there.
- Cheers.
Was it okay when I carried you?
Yeah, no worries.
Good job.
You weren't heavy.
Thanks.
I wonder what they're up to.
I'm curious too.
GANGNEUNG
SEONGYOJANG HOUSE
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
- Thank you.
Yes, you're right.
This is a yangban's house.
What's a yangban?
It means "nobleman."
What? Isn't yangban
what a wife calls his husband?
Yangban…
"Hey, you stupid yangban."
Isn't that it?
No, isn't it a nobleman?
Yangban?
Seobang!
Hey, so I was right.
KOREAN IS SO DIFFICULT
Okay, like this.
GANGNEUNG
KIAN'S B&B
WOLJEONGSA TEMPLE
GUEST JUN-HO
Relaxation is at the core
of Buddhist meditation.
Gosh, it's huge.
I should exercise a bit here.
PRACTICING SUNMUDO
THE B&B STAFF ARRIVES AT SKY RANCH
Jun-ho, I'm glad I came.
Right?
We need to rest
and recharge ourselves too.
- There are sheep.
- Yeah.
They look so cute.
Gosh, they're so cute.
Aren't they babies? Over there.
- They're so small.
- Are they sleeping?
They're so cute.
- It's a baby.
- It's so cute.
They're so cute.
The lambs are so cute.
It must be a guest.
They're here?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hello.
Hello, is this the boss of Kian's B&B's?
Yes, it is.
I'll be checking in as a guest today.
I see. Hello.
Yes, hello.
How many of you are there?
I'm by myself.
- By yourself?
- Yes.
Then, you can come by 4:00 p.m.
3:10 P.M.
I'll send you the address,
and you can go there.
I understand.
Okay, see you then.
See you then. Bye.
It's near the reservoir.
DAY 2, 4:00 P.M.
1 GUEST WILL CHECK IN
Next to Doam Lake.
We have another guest.
How many?
- One.
- One person?
- It's just one.
- Let's go.
I have a feeling more will come.
I'm getting another call.
What?
- For real?
- What on earth?
Hello?
Hello? My name's Chae Seul,
and I'm checking in today.
Hello.
CONSTANT CHECK-IN CALLS MAKE THEM NERVOUS
I'll send you the address.
You can come after 4:00 p.m.
How many of you are there?
- I'm by myself.
- By yourself?
Okay, bye.
KIAN'S B&B DAY 2
2 GUESTS WILL CHECK IN
I think we'll be back in time
to greet them.
- We should go back now.
- Let's go work.
THEY RETURN AFTER BRIEFLY
GETTING SOME FRESH AIR
All the snow's melted.
- You're right.
- That was quick.
It's a shame it melted so fast.
It looked so nice though.
THE WEATHER HAS BEEN WARM ALL DAY
IT WAS SNOWY AROUND KIAN'S B&B
UNTIL THIS MORNING
It really must have been warm today.
THE SNOW DISAPPEARED WITHOUT A TRACE
But the wind is cold.
DAEGWALLYEONG'S EVER-CHANGING WEATHER
Every time I come here, it's so bizarre.
It seems to get bigger.
Hey, today,
you two open it.
My knees. My knees hurt.
Should I carry you on my shoulders?
- What do we do?
- Should I?
Her knees hurt.
You carry her on your shoulders.
- Should I?
- Is that possible?
SHE GETS IN POSITION WITHOUT HESITATION
Let's do it.
Look at her posture.
- You have to go lower. Yeah.
- Lower?
- Yeah. Give it a try.
- Wait.
- She says she works out a lot.
- Hold onto me.
- Okay.
Hold on.
- One, two, three.
- It's working.
Come on. Hurry.
- Hurry.
- I got it.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Zuha!
- Wait!
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu